Good evening.
こんばんは
ERROR
りんかさん?
Yes, I'm Rinka.
はい、りんかです
Rinka-san?
りんかさん?
cute.
かわいい
Isn't Rinka-chan cute?
りんかちゃん、かわいくない?
No, no.
いやいや
How old are you?
何歳?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
That's right, I'm 18 years old.
だよね、18歳だよね
Yes, you look a little younger, but
そうだよね、もうちょっと若く見えるけど、
You're not a minor.
未成年じゃないよね
No, I'm an adult.
いえ、成年してます
ERROR
でね、18だよね
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
Then, what kind of work do you do?
したらさ、仕事は何やってる子なんですか?
ERROR
仕事は今、介護職やってます
I worked as a nurse.
介 護職してんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
ERROR
そっか、寒くない?
today.
今日
It's cold today, isn't it?
今日寒いですね
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いよね
It's really cold, isn't it?
めちゃくちゃ寒いよね
It's cold at night.
夜は寒いです
It's cold.
寒いね
Wait a minute?
ちょっと待った?
ERROR
いえいえ、すぐ
this.
これ
Really?
本当に?
Shiro looks good on me.
なんか、シロが似合うね
I love Shiro.
シロ大好きです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's pure white.
真っ白だもんね
真っ白です
What are your hobbies and what do you like?
趣味とか、何が好きなの?
Favorite food, favorite food?
好きな食べ物、好きな食べ物ですか?
What food do you like?
食べ物、何が好きなの?
I like food and sweet things.
食べ物、甘いもの好きです
Do you like sweets?
甘いもの好きなの?
I see.
そうか
Sweets, what, sweets, things like that?
甘いもの、何、お菓子とか、そういうの?
I like sweets, and I also like flats.
お菓子も好きだし、フレーツも好きだし
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
yes.
はい
I like everything.
何でも好きです
ERROR
何でも好きなんだ
It's just that I like sweets.
なんか甘いもの好きっていうだけであれだよね
You're young, aren't you?
若いよね
You're young, or rather childish.
若いっていうか、子供っぽいよね
I agree.
そうですね
I see.
そうか
I think it's fine.
ごさまだと思います
Really?
本当に?
cute.
可愛い
Then I guess I'll go eat something sweet.
したらじゃあ甘いもの食べに行っちゃおうかな
ERROR
甘いもの食べに行きたいです
It's a bit nighttime.
ちょっと夜だからさ
ERROR
ちょっとやってるあれが限られちゃうけどさ
Let's just go eat something light and sweet.
ちょっとじゃあ軽く甘いものだけ食べに行こうか
Well then, let's ask a few questions.
じゃあそこでさ、ちょっとさ、いろいろちょっと聞いていこう
kana.
かな
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫 です
OK, let's go then.
OK、じゃあ行こうか
Let's go.
行きましょう
Inca-chan.
インカちゃん
yes.
はい
It's here.
来たね
来ましたね
It's here.
来たね
I can eat sweets after all.
やっぱ甘いもの食べれるね
You can eat it.
食べれますね
Okay, eat.
いいよ、食べて
Eat, eat.
食べて食べて
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Yes, please go ahead.
はい、どうぞどうぞ
What is that?
何それ?
It's matcha.
抹茶です
Matcha?
抹茶?
cute.
かわいい
Please show me.
見せてくれな
here you are
はい、どうぞ
delicious.
美味しい
delicious?
美味 しい?
It's warm.
温まります
Does it warm you?
温まる?
ERROR
今日寒いよね、ちょっとね
It's cold.
寒いね
Hey, I'm sorry.
ちょっとさ、ごめんね
While I'm eating, I think I'd like to ask you some questions.
食べながらさ、 ちょっといろいろ質問していきたいなと思うんだ
But.
けど さ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
ERROR
ちょっとモラルのない質問ばっかりしちゃうと思うけど
good?
いい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
here you are
はい、どうぞ
As Rinka-chan said at the beginning,
りんかちゃんはさ、 その冒頭でも言ってたけどさ、
ERROR
あれでしょ、介護職してるでしょ?
はい、介護職してます
Nursing jobs, home-visit nursing care, etc.
介護職ってさ、 訪問介護とかさ、
Is it a nursing home?
老人ホームだっけ?
There's a lot of things going on.
なんかあんじゃん、いっぱい
I have a gift for you.
資礼がありますね
Oh, are you doing everything?
あ、全部やってんの?
that.
それ
Oh, I'm a visiting caregiver.
あ、自分は訪問介護ですね
Oh, I'm doing home-visit nursing care.
あ、訪問介護のほうやってんだ
Like visiting your home?
お宅に訪問みたいな?
I agree.
そうですね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
What do you mean by visiting nursing care?
訪問介護ってさ、なんていうの?
It's like visiting, right?
訪問して、みたいな感じでしょ?
I will visit.
訪問します
That's right, grandparents, right?
それはさ、おじいちゃんおばあちゃんでしょ?
Are there many grandpas?
おじいちゃんやっぱ多いの?
There are many.
多いです
Really?
本当に?
That's right, it's home-visit nursing care.
ていうことはだよ、訪問介護じゃん
I'm going to take care of you.
介護するんだよね
I will provide care.
介護します
That being said, my grandpa's grandpa was
ていうことはだけどさ、おじいちゃんのおじいちゃんは、
So you've seen a lot?
いっぱい見たことあるってこと?
Yes, there is.
ありますね
That's right.
そうだよね
To be honest, it's my grandfather.
ぶっちゃけさ、おじいちゃんってさ、
Grandpa isn't standing?
おじいちゃん立ってない?
It's soft.
柔らかいです
soft?
柔らかい?
It's soft.
柔らかいです
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
I see.
そっか
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだよね
I can't stand there too long,
あんまりビンビン立ってられるとこさ、
You'll be in trouble.
困っちゃうよね
I'm in trouble.
困っちゃいます
You'll be in trouble.
困っちゃうよね
more.
もっと
ERROR
りんかちゃんはさ、なんか趣味とかあんの?
What are your hobbies?
趣味は?
Like singing a song.
歌を歌ってるとか
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I go on trips.
旅行に行ったりする
picture?
え?
Is your boyfriend okay?
彼氏はいいの?
There isn't one.
いないね
Don't you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いない?
Do you ever travel alone without a boyfriend?
彼氏いないで、一人旅行って一人行ったりとか?
One person, yes.
一人とか、そうです
Family, friends, etc.
家族とか、友達とか
That's right.
そうなんだ
I'm 18 years old, but I'm alone.
18歳でさ、だけどさ、一人でさ、
Traveling is such a drastic thing.
旅行ってさ、すごい思い切ったやつだよね
That's pretty good, isn't your footwork light?
かなりさ、フットワーク軽くない?
It might be lighter.
軽い方かもしれない
That's amazing.
すごいね
We've been together for 18 years now.
今までさ、18年間さ、付き合ってきた、
When I was a teenager, a high school student, and a high school girl,
産生、高校生、JK時代だったりさ、
How much?
どんぐらい?
2 people.
2人
2 people?
2人?
Huh?
あれ?
10 million?
1000万?
Who is your boyfriend now?
今、彼氏は?
I'm not there right now.
今は、いないです
Free Ann now?
今、フリーアン?
I'm not there.
いないです
That's right.
そうなんだ
Whether it's a nursing job or a part-time job,
介護職とかでさ、アルバイトとかでさ、
Don't you have any encounters?
出会いとかないの?
To be honest, I don't have many encounters.
出会いは、正直あんまりなくて
Well, not really.
まあ、ないよね
If that's the job.
そういう仕事だったらね
That's right.
そうだよね
Well, what do you call that kind of part-time job?
いや、そういうアルバイト先、何て言うの?
Do you mean employee?
社員って言うの?
Isn't there?
ないの?
Not really, yes.
あんまり、そうですね
I didn't work much.
自分は結構仕事しなかった
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Never before.
今までなかった
There isn't much of a music career effect.
音楽職効果とかもあんまりなくて
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
People have no meaning.
人の意味がなくて
I don't do that kind of work.
そんな仕事してない
Seriously?
マジで?
What do you say, Ginga-chan?
銀河ちゃんはさ、またさ、なんていうの?
How do you know you don't have a job?
どうしてさ、仕事ないの分かってんの?
We're together.
一緒だって
Got it.
分かった
Why are you so cute?
どうして、こんなにさ、可愛いさ、
You're such a serious kid, why are you so serious?
本当、真面目な子がさ、なんでそんなに、
That's what I thought.
って思ったからさ
What, what is it?
なんだ、なんなの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
When I was in junior high school, I watched an erotic video for the first time.
中学生の時に、初めてエッチな動画を見てしまって、
I was interested from there.
そこから興味があった
It was Ginga-chan.
銀河ちゃんだった
Seriously?
マジで?
It's not super naughty.
超エッチじゃないですよ
I was interested in doing it with just the two of us.
二人でするんだって、興味があった
At first I was satisfied.
最初は満足してた
I was satisfied with myrcene, but...
ミルセンで満足してたけど、みたいな
But I want to try it myself.
でも、自分もやってみたい
Now.
今の
Seriously?
マジで?
Really?
本当に?
But, you two have dated before, right?
だけどさ、付き合ったことあるのが二人でしょ?
Yeah.
うん
How many people have experience?
経験人数は?
same?
同 じ?
It's the same.
同じです
A boyfriend or an ex-boyfriend?
彼氏だったり、元彼だったりっていう?
Are you a boyfriend or do you have two ex-boyfriends?
彼氏ですか、元彼が二人っていう?
Yes, that's right.
うん、そうですよ
Seriously?
マジか
So is it okay to have a third person?
それでじゃあ三人目いいんですか?
Yes, the third one.
うん、三人目
Seriously?
マジで?
So what?
じゃあ何?
Things like the plays I watched through the screen at Milsen.
ミルセンで画面越しで見てたプレーだったりとかっていうのを、
I also wanted to experience it, so I applied.
私も体験したいから、ちょっと応募してみました、
What?
的な?
It seems like I got caught up in this old guy.
こんなおじさんに引っかかっちゃいましたみたいな
Thank you for your great curiosity.
すごい好奇心お世話だね
Actually traveling alone...
本当 に一人旅するっていうのも、
I thought it was rather light.
なんかとは軽いなと思ってたけどさ
So far, it's kind of amazing that it's him.
ここまでね、ちょっと彼だとすごいね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I was surprised.
びっくりして
So, do you like such naughty ladies?
じゃあ、そういうエッチなお姉さんが好きなの?
Oh, that's naughty.
ああ、エッチなの
You like naughty things, right?
エッチなことが好きなんでしょう?
I want to get into a naughty profession.
エッチな職業とかにつきたいなっていうのはさ、
Don't you think so?
思わないの?
I don't think so.
思わない
そういうのは思わないんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
Also, it's a little different.
またそれとはちょっと違うんだ
Yes, there are adult entertainment venues.
あるじゃん、風俗場とか
I don't think I want to be involved in something like that.
そんなのにつきたいなと思わないんだ
Yeah, I don't think so.
そう、そう思わない
I see.
そっか
After all, I'm interested in AV, that kind of thing.
やっぱりじゃあAVっていう、そういうのに興味あるんだね
yes.
そう
ERROR
AVって
Well then, I understand.
じゃあ、分かった
Well, the uncles are going to listen to the lecture today.
じゃあもうおじさんたちが今日、聴教しちゃうから
Teaching.
聴教
I think it's just my first time playing,
初めてのプレイばっかりだと思うけど、
That's right, if you don't have any experience.
そんだけね、経験がなかったら
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Do you want to try it?
やってみたいの?
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Will you do your best?
頑張ってくれるの?
fun.
楽しみ
Looks fun.
楽 し そう
Well then, what should I say?
そ したらじゃあさ、なんていうの
I'll do it even if you take it home.
持ち帰ってもやるから
I wonder what I'll say again.
ちょっとまた、さ、なんて言うんだろう
I guess I'll take you to the hotel right away.
すぐホテルに連れてっちゃうかな
Are you seriously okay?
マジで大丈夫?
Really?
本当に?
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is everyone probably watching this?
これたぶんみんな見てる?
Will everyone see it?
みんな見る?
Will you look at it?
見てくれますかね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Understood.
わかった
Okay, so that's what happened recently at a hotel.
じゃあ、そういうことだから、最近ホテルで
Yes, please.
はい、お願いされます
Rinka-chan.
りんかちゃん
It's Rinka.
りんかでーす
Good evening.
こんばんは
Good evening, you've arrived at the hotel.
こんばんはっていうか、ホテル来たね
It's coming.
来ちゃいましたね
But in a bright place, just like before,
でも明るいところでさ、さっきもさ、
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's embarrassing.
はずかしいです
Is it embarrassing?
は ずかしい?
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
Try looking up a little.
ちょっと上目遣いしてみて
nice.
いいね
cute.
かわいい
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してますね
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Well, what is it?
まあさ、なんだっけ、
I thought I'd take her to a hotel before she changes her mind.
ちょっと 気持ち変わんないうちにホテル連れ込んじゃおうと、
I brought her to a hotel, but...
ホ テ ル 連れ込んできたけどさ、
I thought you wanted to ask me something a little while ago.
さっきさ、ちょっとさ聞きたかったなと思ったんだけどさ、
There were a lot of customers around, so...
周りにさ、お客さんとかいっぱいいたからさ、
It was a difficult atmosphere to listen to, so I screamed.
聞きづらい雰囲気だったからさ、 キュロキュロキュロキュロした
Well.
も んね
It's Curikyu.
キュリキューって
That's why I thought I shouldn't ask too much.
だから、ちょっとあまり聞いちゃいけないなと思ったからさ、
That was it, but why are you so interested in AV?
あれだったんだけどさ、 なに、AVそんな興味あんの?
I agree.
そうですね
I've been watching it since I was in middle school.
中学生の頃から見てました
Seriously?
マジで?
Well, what kind of genre is AV?
そのさ、AVっていうのはさ、 どういうジャンル的なもので言
What?
った らさ?
There are quite a lot of things that amateurs see.
結構、素人の見ることが多くて
Well then, Linka-chan is just like that.
じゃあ、リンカちゃんそのまんまじゃん
Isn't it?
じゃない?
Is that so?
そうですかね
Amateur viewing?
素人の見るの?
Apparently he's an amateur.
素人のそうです
What else?
あとは?
Also, the actress is actually in it, etc.
あとは女優さんが本当に出ているものだったりとか、
Girls also like being attacked.
女 の子も攻められているのが好きです
Are you doing research?
研究すんの?
You're doing research.
研究してますんですね
That's right.
そうなんだ
She's such a naughty girl.
すごいエッチな子だね
It might be naughty.
エッチかもしれないです
By the way, do you like sex?
ちなみに、エッチは好きなの?
I like it.
好きです
Do you like being bullied?
いじめられるのも好きなの?
I like blow jobs.
フ ェ ラ は好きです
Do you like blowjobs?
フェラは好きなの?
I also like blowjobs.
フェラも好きです
Did Japan add Chinchin?
ちんちんを加えたのは日本?
Only in Japan.
日本だけです
That means it's the third one.
3本目ということだね
I agree.
そうですね
I will be the third person in many ways.
いろいろ3人目になります
It's only the third one.
まだ3本目だよね
What if it was normal or 18 years old?
それが普通か18歳だったら?
surely.
確かに
Maybe so.
そうかもしれない
How big were your two dicks so far?
今まで2つのチンポ、どれくらい大きかった?
Try expressing it with your hands.
手で表してみて
How long was it?
どれくらいだった?
lie?
うそ?
Really?
本当に?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Well, in AV, there are actors with big dicks.
よくさ、AVとかでさ、大きいチンコの男優さんとかいるじゃん
What do you think about that?
ああいうのはさ、どうなの?
Well, it looks like Yets.
えー、イエツみたい
That's naughty.
エッチだね
It's so naughty.
すごいエッチなんだね
You like it.
好きなんだね
I agree.
そうですね
He's such a good kid.
めちゃくちゃ良い子じゃん
Shall we go quickly?
早く行ってしちゃおうか
yes.
はい
Given the situation, I think I'll do a lot.
状況じゃあいっぱいしていこうかな
Please tell me the situation.
状況お願いします
Yes, I was asked to do so.
はい、お願いされました
I'm the third person.
3本目の人です
The third person.
3本目の人
Is it okay?
いいんかね?
Yes, I heard that.
はい、聞いてました
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
Someone who likes AV, huh?
AV好きの人か、ちゃん
I like AV.
A V好き
You'll have to leave on your own.
自分で出ることになるからね
You guys.
お 前らが
お前らが
It's debut today.
今日デビューだね
I'm making my debut.
デビューしちゃいます
You're about to make your debut.
デビューしちゃうんだね
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
I agree.
そうですね
I'm nervous.
緊張してる
What are you looking forward to, or rather excited about?
楽しみっていうか、ドキドキ、ワクワク的なところは?
There are already quite a few.
もう結構ありますね
Is there quite a lot?
結 構ある?
What is the percentage?
割合は?
The percentage is...
割合は...
I'm looking forward to 7.
7が楽しみです
Are you looking forward to 7?
7が楽しみ?
I guess 3 makes me feel anxious.
3が不安みたいな感じですかね
The ratio was the opposite.
逆かとなった割合
It turned out to be the opposite.
逆かとなった
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみが
easy
楽
Shimiga.
し みが
Hitoka-chan's body is also a bit...
人かちゃんも体がちょっと...
What's up with this outfit?
この洋服はどうなってるの?
That's about it.
そここれですね
There?
そ こで?
I was more excited.
俺のほうがドキドキしてきた
My heart is pounding.
ドキドキしちゃいます
What's next?
次は?
Next, I'll take this off.
次は、これを脱いちゃいます
Shall I take it off?
脱いちゃいます?
yes.
はい
Let's show it.
見せましょう
It's funny.
ふかしい
That's fine.
いいじゃん
I haven't smoked it.
ふかしておらん
You can even put one up.
1つも立てていいよ
Show me your body.
ちょっと体見せて
Take that.
それ持って
Wow, what is that?
うわ、なにそれ
Is it somehow transparent?
なんか透けてんの?
Isn't it transparent?
透けてない?
Want to compete?
勝負したい?
I want to compete.
勝負したい
cute.
かわいい
picture?
え?
Isn't it transparent?
透けてない?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I'll do something more embarrassing.
もっと恥ずかしいことするよ
Try to keep it in your pants.
そのままパンツ食い込ませてみて
pants?
パンツ?
It's like a tea bag.
ティーバックみたいにしてる
Try pushing it in a little harder.
もうちょっとガッツリ食い込ませてみて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Try becoming colored.
カラメになってみて
Oh, naughty.
あら、えっち
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Are you shaking your ass?
お尻フリフリしてんの?
Will it wriggle?
くねくねしちゃうの?
Wiggle.
くねくね
It's twisting.
くねくねしちゃうのね
Okay, you can look ahead.
いいよ、前見ていいよ
Sit down.
座って
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's taken a lot.
すっごい取られてるね
It gets taken away a lot.
すっごい取られちゃう
It was taken until autumn.
秋まで取られちゃったよ
秋まで取られちゃった
Yo.
よ
Are you going to sleep in your pants?
パ ンツ寝ちゃう?
You can sit down.
座っていいよ
That's it,
これでさ、
Hey, can you become an MG?
ちょっと じゃあMGになってもらえる?
Or put your feet up.
足を上にやるとか
I'll go a little earlier.
もうちょっと前行きます
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
So, yeah, yeah, yeah.
で、ちょっと そうそうそう
Just open it up.
ちょっと開いてみて
Give me a cup.
ク パちょうだい
Do you understand Kupa?
クパわかる?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
You've never been taken, right?
取られたことないでしょ
No.
ないです
first time.
初めて
It's your first time.
初めてだよね
Yeah.
うん
So, how about Linka-chan?
じゃあ、リンカちゃんか
I don't really like it.
あんまり嫌だよね
I haven't used toys that much yet.
まだおもちゃとかもそんなに使ったことない
There are no toys.
おもちゃない
Well, since we have a special day today, I'd like to buy some toys.
じゃあ今日はせっかくだから、 ちょっとおもちゃとかもちょっと
Try using it
使 ってみる
mosquito.
か
Linka-chan, spread it out a little.
リ ンカちゃん、ちょっと広げて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I heard a very naughty sound.
くちゃくちゃエッチな音がしてきたよ、
Linka-chan.
リンカちゃん
Ho
ほ
and others.
ら
It feels good.
気 持ちいいな
Spread your pussy properly.
ちゃんと広げていっておまんこ
Pussy.
おまんこ
Once a day.
1回1日に
Relax and see.
力抜いてほら
amazing.
すごい
Your pussy is so tight, Rinka-chan.
きついね、リンカちゃん、おまんこが
The toys are amazing.
おもちゃすごい
amazing?
すごい?
Did it become a mess?
ぐしゃぐしゃになっちゃった?
It became a mess.
ぐっちゃぐちゃになっちゃった
Linka-chan, this is already a mess.
リンカちゃん、 なんかもうぐっちゃぐちゃだよ、
this.
これ
It's become a mess.
ぐっちゃぐちゃになっちゃったじゃん
Hey Linka-chan,
ちょっとリンカちゃん、
The sofa was old, but it was covered in salt.
ソ ファーゆずびたしだけど、 塩びたしか
I fell asleep there for a while, so
ちょっともうそこ寝ちゃったから、
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっちおいで
Ah, amazing.
あーすごい
Just look.
見るだけね
It's fine just to look.
見るだけならいいよ
Yes, go here.
はい、ここに行ってごらん
Third one?
3本目?
This is the third one.
3本目です
I saw the third one.
3本目見ちゃったね
I saw it.
見ちゃった
I said I'd just watch it.
見るだけって言ったんだって
Just look.
見るだけだよって
vinegar
す
It's birthday day.
げ え日ですね
yes?
そう?
You seem to be wanting something.
なんか物欲しそうだね
what happened?
どう したの?
I wanted it.
欲しくなっちゃいました
yeah?
ん?
What do you want?
何が欲しい?
Chin chin.
ちんちん
I wanted it.
欲しくなっちゃいました
What should I do?
どうする?
Pikari is already touching it.
ピカリがもう触ってるしね
Okay then.
じゃあいいよ
You can do whatever you like.
好きにしていいよ
good
好
tree.
き
Is it okay if I eat dick?
ち んちん食べちゃっていいんですか?
Couldn't you have said okay?
いいって言うかもなかったの?
Yeah.
うん
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
I'm becoming human.
人間になってる
Yeah.
うん
Hey Enka, you're pretty good at something.
ちょっとエンカさん、だいぶ何か上手だけど
Quite what?
だいぶ何?
Did you prepare for this by reading the AV?
これはAV読みって予習してきたの?
yes.
はい
I have already prepared.
予習しちゃいました
Isn't it too much preparation?
予習しすぎじゃない?
I want it if I have too much preparation.
予習すぎちゃったら欲しい
My dick is delicious.
ちんちんが美味しくて
licking.
ペロペロ
I'm becoming human.
人間になってる
Do you like being deep inside?
奥までいるの好きなの?
Do you like pain too?
苦しいのも好きなの?
like.
好き
That's amazing.
すごいね
I want to move back a little.
ちょっと後ろかかしたい